HANDSON YAMAZAKI
I want to talk about the beauty of instrumental music!
I am Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。 This is Rio Sakurai from Morning Musume' 13.
We have a guest again this time in this corner.
Yes, I'm Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume'13. This is Yabe Min from Tsubaki Factory.
Thank you very much.
I'm very happy. Thank you very much.
I'm happy too.
Talking with Riley was like when we passed each other at a concert together.
It's like I talked to her on my own.
I'm so happy.
You can't even talk to her eye-to-eye.
So I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
We're talking a lot, but I think it would be nice to get to know each other a little better.
Let's ask each other questions.
Questions?
A totally unrelated, common question.
Are you from Tokyo?
Yes, I was born in Tokyo. I was born in Tokyo.
Three good things about Tokyo.
Three!
There are many ways to get around.
Beautiful night view.
Night view?
What should I do?
You can always go out and enjoy it.
You like the night view?
I like the night view.
You like it?
I love it.
Really?
Let's go together sometime.
Let's go.
Are you sure about that?
Are you sure?
He said he's been researching me.
Really?
I was so surprised. Me too.
I love him.
Can I ask you a question?
Well, you have this.
This is,
Sesan 2!
I'm a finger-painter.
Really?
You're a Sessan fan?
What? You know Sessan?
I also know of Sessan.
There's also that one. Yes, I know.
There's also living in Issei.
There's also Issei.
Yes, there is.
That's what I wanted to hear.
We had a lot of fun.
It was fun.
Yes, it was. So, let's get down to business.
I would like to introduce three songs by Tsubaki Factory.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please introduce the first song from Mr. 4 minutes.
I am Fuwari Koi Clock.
It is the fifth single with a release date of February 27, 2019.
The fifth one.
So this song was released when I was not yet in the tour captain,
I was really surprised when I heard it.
It's a lovely song.
First of all, from before the chorus to the chorus,
Before the chorus, it is a bit quiet.
It's calm.
Calm and quiet,
I thought it was a good representation of her character.
And then, after the chorus, what do you call it that she's hiding deep inside?
Emotions?
Yes. It's like her voice is released.
You can feel it once, so please listen to it.
Please listen to it.
Thank you very much.
What do you call this part yet?
Slowly.
It means "soft love clock.It represents Fluffy Love Clock.
I don't know.
It's in there slowly.
Put your hand over the bell.
You can hear it popping.
Right here?
There's a buzzing sound coming from here.
And then the flowers and butterflies...
You're right. It's autumn.
That's where the hidden voice comes from.
Around here...
Like the violin...
It's like it's spreading out.
Let me explain a little bit about this clock.
You heard the booming sound at the beginning, right?
Then came the chorus, and the girl's secret love was released.
Then, a lot of instruments were added, right?
Before that, it was slow, and if you plugged the bell with your hand and pinged it, it would make a sound.
A little thumping sound.
It sounded like that.
A kind of muffled sound.
So it's like you haven't fully let it out yet, or it's stuck in that bell alone.
It's like if you had a hard time in love or something, it was released in the chorus.
The door opened with a bang.
And the tick-tock, tick-tock of the clock,
Luna thought that it was probably her,
I was feeling, you know, like I was nervous.
Accompanying it was the thumping sound of the clock.
Koi doi ichikkuu Taku, are you going to play Yoshihiko Ishii? I said, "Yes, I am,
It's like they are in a hurry.
So I thought they were getting more and more nervous,
I thought this part was amazing.
The sound of "two" after the clock at the end is so beautiful,
It's solving with a bang.
From 2 minutes 44 seconds to 3 minutes 25 seconds.
It's between my impressions.
I think I probably like it a lot.
I really love all the songs.
I think "Fuwari Koi Clock" is about love.
It's probably about the love I think,
There were many people who closed their hearts to me. The door.
There you go.
And then, she said that a new love will start again,
I open the door in the chorus,
I remember the many things that have happened in the past.
It's about the past, isn't it? I see.
That's right. So the sound is a bit rushed.
Please, for now, go ahead.
What's that?
Wow!
It's like we're going back in time.
It's like...
Like a playback in reverse.
It's like time and space are warped.
And from here...
It's so slow!
The piano makes it sound like a radio.
And here...
The piano is very strong.
Wow!
Piano is already feeling like a love clock.
Now that feeling has overtaken the rest of the music in my impression, and only the piano is going "aha".
It's like she realized her feelings in her impressions.
But I really understood your impression.
I could tell that you have been through a lot in the past.
Yes, that's right. You can definitely understand, can't you?
Keiko Koeda is not here.
You told me that. The sound.
Let me give you an example.
There is Piano-chan.
Let's say that this Piano-chan is Keiko Koeda's feelings.
The impression is that there are all kinds of sounds around the piano.
That is my impression.
As the piano goes on and on, all the fuzz around it melts away and the piano becomes the sole focus of her attention.
You said that they are no longer there.
That's right. Then the piano became one,
The true feelings inside the piano appeared with a bang.
That's what I think.
From 3 minutes and 36 seconds.From 3 minutes and 36 seconds.
Here you go.
The last chorus, right here.
Hey Aaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
And this is the very last part,
A lot has happened up to now,
I think we're going to break the clock and start all over again.
Wow!
I don't know.
I totally understand.
The sound has a great sense of storytelling.
The sound of the clock is not like the life of a love clock girl, but it is a story,
It's more of a reminiscence.
Clock Girl's music is
I think the sound of the clock is like an aura of the atmosphere and scenery around the clock. It's like a music box that is playing at the same time.
Does a music box change at the same time as time? Yes, it does. Is it like that? I understand music boxes very well. Maybe that's it. Even during a live performance. It makes me go "huh".
Next, I, Sakurai, would like to introduce you. I would like to introduce "Seishun Manchu" (full of youth).
This is the first single released on September 6, 2015.
It is a song that gives me goosebumps in a good way from the intro. I love this song so much that I saw Mr. Tsubaki perform it at Hinayoshi 23.
I was so impressed by it that I brought this song to the show.
The first point is the A melody.
At first, only one note is used for the rhythm, but after that, there are more notes in the back of the melody.
What?
You can tell that there are more notes.
I want to listen to it.
First of all, I would like you to listen to the part of the first A melody where the back-taking increases. Go ahead!
It's true.
It's true!
And then, after that, there are more notes, right?
Then, this tutti sound became a little bit quieter.
Really!
I often listen to music with the bass enhanced. I often enhance the bass sound when I listen to instrumental music.
When I do that, the rhythm sounds really loud.
This one has more of the rhythm sound of the first conton than the others.
I just wanted to introduce this one.
Bass subject?
Bass subject.
It sounds like a bass burn.
I'm sure it is.
I didn't really notice.
I didn't really notice it, but it's live.
I think it's because it's instrumental that you can hear it so well.
Next, I really like the interlude of this song.
It's the sound that goes quiet for a moment and then rises to a crescendo,
It's called a crescendo, and then it becomes a falling sound.
My brain is amazing!
No, no, no!
That's right.
It's very easy to understand that it's a crescendo and the sound becomes smaller and smaller,
You're saying it in a man's voice.
This seisyun, last week's vocal echoes are like being under water. It's like being in water.
There is no sound, and I really like to hear this muffled sound, so please listen to it.
Specific
It's going up again.
The difference between going down and going up is really cool.
Tsubaki's interludes are really wonderful, and the interlude in the previous song "Fuwari Koitoki" was really good.
Sometimes I just repeat the interlude forever.
Wow! Just the interlude.
The opening of the interlude is a break and the sound stops for a while.
For example, in morning songs, after the opening of the interlude, there are many times when the song suddenly starts to drop into a chorus with a booming accent.
But in this song, there is a break and then a stop before the accent.
When I listen to instrumental music, I also use bass enhancement while watching the waveform of the sound.
It's something like this.
A heartbeat?
Yes. When the sound gets louder, it becomes like this.
I listen to it while watching the sound waveform,
The sound waveform doesn't disappear at the break.
It is a break, but there is a little sound in it.
So I thought it was just a blank sound, but there was a little rhythm in it,
I could see it visually.
I'd like to listen to it.
Now, let's listen to the break after the impression.
Hmm...
BREAK.
Amazing.
DUN DUN DUN DUN.
Amazing!
It's a break, but there's a sound in it, and it's amazing.
I really like it when it's a break but it's not a break.
It's amazing!
It's like it's breaking the rules.It's kind of like, you know, it's like it's defying common sense.
It's like they don't just stop at BREAK.
It's like they are right behind you. It's like he's got a real presence.
It's like, "I'm here in Chishima.
That's for sure. That's really true.
Wow! That's what I meant.
I thought that kind of sound was the cool part.
Once you perform this, I hope you will sing it someday.
I want to do it.
The choreography is also "dun, dun, dun, dun.
I think it's a great accent.
I think it would be a lot of fun. I'm sure it would be a lot of fun.
I want to do it so much.
Please do it.
I'm so happy to hear you say that about our songs,
I'm going to cry. I'm not going to cry.
It's not a mistake. I won't cry.
It's our 10th single, released on February 22, 2023.
It's a song that came out after I joined Tsuba Caff Tree,
I had confidence in it.
Because we could make it together.
I was wrong for 0.52 minutes.
0.52 seconds?
Wait.
From about 0:52 to 1:31,
It's just a little bit longer,
Anyway, I can't explain it,
I can't explain it, so I'm going to go ahead and ask.
Go ahead!
It's so easy to understand.
I'd totally understand if you were singing,
I wish it was in the back.
You know what I mean? In the back,
I don't know how to say it,
It's hard to notice if you're singing.
It's a foreshadowing.
I want you to hear it. Wait a minute.
I'm going to say what I think about the relationship between this song and music,
I'm not mistaken, this music is not crying,
It's like a soft kiss.
Shigoshi?
It's not a mistake, I'm protecting you,
It's like I'm walking with her.
In the A and B melodies, she's like a strong and timid girl,
So the music is very strong,
But after the chorus, high notes such as violins start to appear.
And then she says the lyrics aren't wrong,
She says, "It still hurts right now, but...,
He said it was more like he was feeling really good than being bullish.
It's like he's really feeling it.
It's a little bit positive, but it's like my true heart is coming out,
Violin is crying a little.
The violinist was crying a lot,
I thought it was a representation of that sadness,
I want you to listen to the sound here and here,
Here you go.
This violin.
The sound,
Ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong.
I understand.
Ding-dong-katten, dong-dong-katten.
I see.
And then..,
The first and second choruses are still "shoo".
It's always "shoo",
The story of this song is pretty bad.
I wanted you to know that it's a shoe,
I'm going to leave the story for now,
I'll tell you a different story.
Before the chorus,
Tentententententententententententententententententententententententententententent
Tententententententententententententententententententententententententententent.
The lyrics of "Duk duk duk duk duk duk duk duk duk duk duk duk duk duk duk duk duk duk,
The second chorus is also the lyric, "Make magic happen to me,
The second chorus is also a lyric about casting a spell,
When I say I'm doing it, I mean I'm still doing it,
It's like I haven't done it yet.
It's like I'm just getting started.
That's why the music is pushing the back of the song forward as well.
I see.I see.
Then it's in the chorus.
The lyrics and the sound are combined.
But from about 3 minutes and 1 second before the last chorus,
I'd like to listen to the last 3 minutes and 39 seconds.
Go ahead!
Isn't this too much?
That's my favorite break.
The break. That's my favorite break.
And here, too, before the chorus, there's a lyric that says, "Let's go up like this," right?
But only before the last chorus,
But just before the last chorus, it's a new story, the next stage of love, and they're determined.
I'm going to walk to the next stage.
The same part as the A melody and the B melody, but the last chorus is a decision,
Music-chan isn't pushing forward either.
It's not "duk duk duk duk," it's "stop.
There's no mistake. You don't cry.
You were able to go to the chorus even if Ongaku-chan didn't push you.
That's amazing.
Do you understand?
I totally understand.
I thought it was just like that.
That's where the duk-duk-duk should have been,
I'm sure it was there, but I was able to get to the right place inside.
I want you to bring back the one like we talked about earlier.
The one from earlier.
Here it is.
The one about the shoe is also foreshadowed from here,
He said he was able to get there on his own.
Until now, he said "shoo" and stopped,
And then it stopped. Until now.
But..,
That sound you just heard.
It was released.
It was supposed to be Duk-Duk, but it went by its own power.
Next time
Understand?
I understand. I'm not saying it like this, I'm playing it like this.
It's like this.
The chorus, the first and second chorus, there was just shooing and nothing.
But this girl could make up her mind and go, so I broke out the music girl.
Shoo, bang.
So that's what happened.
In the end, though, the guardian god protected the guardian god,
He said he could go do it himself.
That's amazing.
I thought, "Wow, that's great.
This song, as a whole, is about making aluminum foil squishy, right?
When you spread it out, it becomes a little..,
It becomes a little bit nami-nami.
Then you shine light on it.
Then I shined the light on it like this,
The aluminum foil becomes flan, flan, flan, flan, flan.
There are a lot of sounds like that.
There are a lot of sounds like that in the music I'm listening to now, aren't there?
I thought it was a song that made me feel positive.
It's great.
It's done.
The song selection is wonderful.
Moreover, the range of the songs we chose is totally different.
I had a pretty intense sound,
This one was a little sad, or violin.
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
How was it? How was it?
I'm not going to go so far as to talk about the instrumental, but rather, I'm going to use my own words to get the words down.
If it was better, I would write about it on my blog or something.
That's why my vocabulary is still good.
You explained it very well.
Really?
I had a great image in my mind. In my head.
I thought it would be difficult to say it myself,
I thought it was difficult to say it myself, but I thought that just by having people listen to the music, not just by explaining it, we can connect with each other.
I thought it was a universal language. Music.
It really is a universal language. Music.
The comments are great too.
So, please look forward to the next part, where I will introduce the music of Hello!
So, goodbye. Bye bye.
So, when is your birthday?
What is your birthday?Birthday,
I know.
I knew it.
Happy birthday. I know it's past, but it's November.